tallinex.com 2013-07-17

# Tallinex - FX Trading Software

Privacy Policy

At Tallinex Oü, protecting the privacy and safeguarding the personal and financial information of our clients and website visitors is one of our highest priorities. The following statement explains how Tallinex Oü collects and protects your information.

Collected data information

The information Tallinex Oü collects directly from you is required to communicate with you, including your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address; and as required by law, valid credentials to verify your identity such as a passport, government issued ID, and address verification documents. Tallinex Oü also collects demographic information that our clients supply upon initiating a Tallinex Oü account including gender, date of birth, level of education, and occupation, amongst others.

The data is collected from Users during the registration process for Tallinex Oü. In addition, Tallinex Oü collects data related to the clients' trading history.

Tallinex Oü may, by their own initiative, or at the request of the User, complete, correct or delete any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal data.

Disclosure of information

Data will not be disclosed for the purpose of direct advertising, distance selling or other direct marketing, market and public opinion research, or for personal matriculation. The personal data of an individual may be disclosed to a User's superior, in accordance with their own organizational hierarchy. In exceptional circumstances, data may be legally disclosed to a third party upon a request by authorities, to enforce the then valid Operative Agreements and for the possible investigation of possible condition violations and to safeguard the security of Tallinex Oü.

Tallinex Oü may share Tallinex Oü usage information about our website visitors to reputable advertising companies to target our internet banner advertisements on tallinex.com. For this purpose, pixel tags (also called clear gifs or web beacons) may be used to note the pages you have visited, but the information collected by the advertising company through the use of these pixel tags is not personally identifiable.

Tallinex Oü is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of sites that Tallinex Oü may link to, and therefore, have no control over the use or protection of information provided by you or collected by those sites. Whenever you elect to link to a co-branded or linked website, you may be asked to provide registration or other information. Please note that the information you are providing is going to a third party and you should familiarize yourself with the privacy policy provided by therein.

Registry protection

The register is stored on a server protected by the Tallinex Oü´s own password and, therefore, only Tallinex Oü has access to the information contained therein. Use of the information is protected by a username and a password. The register is protected by all appropriate technical and organizational measures. The data is contained within common databases that are protected by usernames, passwords and other technical means. The servers which hold the databases are located in locked premises. The databases are only accessible for processing by such individuals who have been authorized by Tallinex Oü.

Right of inspection

The User has the right to inspect the information held about him/her in the register and do so, free of charge, once per year. If a User wishes to exercise their right of inspection, they must first send a signed inspection request to Tallinex Oü at the address shown below.

Changes

Changes may be made to the privacy policy description which is published on Tallinex Oü´s website. Tallinex Oü will inform those concerned of essential changes via e-mail, by fax, by post or by publishing the information on the Tallinex Oü website.

The holder of the register and the individual taking care of registry matters:

The User has the option to contact the controller at any time at the address below.

Tallinex Oü Company ID:  12358439

Address:  Tornimäe 5, Tallinn, Estonia

Email:  info@tallinex.com

WWW:  www.tallinex.com

If you still have questions that this statement does not address, feel free to contact a client services representative.

Foreign exchange trading involves substantial risk of financial loss, and is not suitable for all.
